Guide to the William Rufus Shafter Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series VII - Printed Reference
  - Copies (Box 8, Folder 80)
Schubert, William Agent at Piedras Negras Roll I Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 6, Folder 7
Schwan, Theodore Col., A. A. G. Roll II Folder 11, Folder 13, Folder 14 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 52
Scorpion (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 21 Roll VI Folder 52
Scott, Irving M. Union Iron Works, San Francisco Roll VI Folder 56
Scott, William Sherley Capt., A. A. G. Roll III Folder 20 Roll IV Folder 39
Scoval, Sylvester Newsman Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 34
Scribner's Magazine Roll VI Folder 50
Scripps McRae League Roll II Folder 16
Scully, James W. Col. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11
Seabaugh, Charles Roll I Folder 8
Seamans, W. H. Roll VI Folder 53
Second Army Corps Roll VI Folder 51
Second Artillary Roll II Folder 16, Folder 18, Folder 19 Roll IV Folder 31 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 57
Second Cavalry Roll III Folder 19, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 35, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 51, Folder 52, Folder 57
Second Georgia Volunteer Infantry Roll II Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19
Second Illinois Volunteer Infantry Roll II Folder 15
Second Infantry Roll II Folder 14, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 24, Folder 27, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 37 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 45, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 52
Second Massachusetts Vol. Infantry Roll II Folder 13, Folder 16, Folder 18 Roll IV Folder 37 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 52
Second New Jersey Vol. Infantry Roll II Folder 17
Second New York Vol. Infantry Roll II Folder 17, Folder 18
Second Pennsylvania Vol. Infantry Roll V Folder 43
Second U. S. Vol. Infantry Roll IV Folder 40, Folder 41
Second Vol. Engineers Roll V Folder 41
Seguranca (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 35, Folder 36 Roll V Folder 44, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 57
Seminole Negro Indian Scouts Roll I Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 6, Folder 7, Folder 8
Seneca (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42 Roll VI Folder 52
Seventeenth U. S. Cavalry Roll I Folder 1
Seventeenth U. S. Colored Troops Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 54, Folder 57
Seventeenth Infantry Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 14, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 33, Folder 37, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 52
Seventh Army Corps Roll II Folder 13, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18
Seventh Artillery Roll VI Folder 51
Seventh Cavalry Roll V Folder 48
Seventh Illinois Vol. Infantry Roll V Folder 47
Seventh Infantry Roll II Folder 13, Folder 16, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 21, Folder 23, Folder 25 Roll IV Folder 35, Folder 37, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50, Folder 52
Seventh Michigan Vol. Infantry Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8 Roll IV Folder 36 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 53, Folder 54, Folder 57
Seventy-first New York Vol. Infantry Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 34, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50, Folder 52, Folder 54
Sewell, Robert Lt., A. A. G. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 25
Sewell, William J. Gen. Roll II Folder 13 Roll III Folder 23
Seyburn, Stephen Y. Lt. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 6, Folder 7
Shafter, Ann Roll I Folder 1
Shafter, Elizabeth Sumner (Shafter's mother) Roll I Folder 8 Roll IV Folder 30 Roll VI Folder 53, Folder 57
Shafter, Harriet A. Grimes (Shafter's wife) Roll I Folder 1, Folder 6, Folder 8 Roll VI Folder 57
Shafter, Howard Roll V Folder 42
Shafter, Hugh M. (Shafter's father) Roll VI Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7
Shafter, James N. (Shafter's brother) Roll I Folder 8 Roll IV Folder 31
Shafter, John Roll IV Folder 37
Shafter, Lauretta (Shafter's Aunt) Roll VI Folder 53
Shafter, Oscar L. Associate Justice of Supreme Court of California Roll I Folder 1 Roll VI Folder 57
Shafter, William Rufus Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7, Folder 8, Folder 9, Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18, Folder 19 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50, Folder 51, Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 54, Folder 55, Folder 56, Folder 57
Shannon, J. R. Asst. Surg. Roll I Folder 2 Roll III Folder 27
Sharpe, Alfred C. Capt., A. A. G. Roll II Folder 13 Roll III Folder 23, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 53, Folder 54
Shayne, Juno F. Roll V Folder 48
Sheridan, Fort Roll VI Folder 53
Sheridan, Philip H. Gen. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 4
Sherman, William T. Gen. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6
Shiba, G. Maj., Japanese Forces Roll III Folder 20 Roll VI Folder 52
Shinnecock (Medical Forces Steamer) Roll V Folder 41, Folder 47
Shirley, Dr. E. L. and Mrs. Roll I Folder 8 B Folder 41, Folder 47
Short, Walter Cowen Lt. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 19
Shoup, George Roll VI Folder 53
Showalter, V. McR. Act. Asst. Surg. Roll V Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48
Siboney, Cuba Roll II Folder 18 Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 43, Folder 44 Roll VI Folder 51, Folder 53, Folder 54, Folder 57
Sicard, Montgomery Rear Admiral, U. S. N. Roll I Folder 9
Signal Corps Roll II Folder 11, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 23, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 37
Signal Corps, Baloon Detachment Roll V Folder 44
Sigsbee, C. D. Capt., U. S. N. Roll III Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll V Folder 41
Simpson, William L. Lt. Roll IV Folder 36, Folder 37
Singer, J. L. Roll I Folder 9
Sixth Cavalry Roll II Folder 13, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19 Roll IV Folder 37, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 45, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50, Folder 52, Folder 54
Sixth Infantry Roll II Folder 16, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 24 Roll IV Folder 37 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 45, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 52
Sixth Illinois Vol. Infantry Roll V Folder 47, Folder 48
Sixth Massachusetts Vol. Infantry Roll VI Folder 54
Sixth Michigan Vol. Infantry Roll IV Folder 36
Sixteenth Infantry Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 24 Roll IV Folder 37 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 52
Sixty-ninth New York Vol. Infantry Roll II Folder 18
Smart, Charles Col. Roll V Folder 48
Smedbery, W. R. Lt. Col. Roll VI Folder 55
Smiley, Samuel E. Lt. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Smith, Charles E. Postmaster Gen. Roll II Folder 11
Smith, Fredick A. Capt., A. A. G. Roll II Folder 11, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 21, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 34
Smith, Harry E. Lt. Roll IV Folder 35 Roll V Folder 44
Smith, I. N. G. A. R. Roll VI Folder 53
Smyth-Stuart, Dr. Ferdinand Capt., British Army Roll IV Folder 35
Snelling, Fort Roll V Folder 45
Sniffen, Culver C. Maj. Roll IV Folder 38 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 45
Snyder, S. Brig. Gen. Roll III Folder 19 Roll VI Folder 57
Socapa Battery Roll III Folder 25 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 36 Roll V Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 57
Society of the Army of Santiago de Cuba Roll IV Folder 37 Roll V Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 53, Folder 54 Roll V Folder 56 Roll VII Folder 65
Society of the Fifth Corps, Army of the Potomac Roll II Folder 14
Special Orders, Hdq., Fifth Army Army Corps, Camp Wikoff Roll V Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50
Spring Hill, Tennessee Roll VI Folder 56
Squadron Bulletin Roll III Folder 20, Folder 22
Squires, Herbert G. Diplomat at Santiago Roll VI Folder 54
Staked Plains, 1872 Roll I Folder 8
Standard Oil Company Roll II Folder 12
Stanley, W. E. Gov., Ohio Roll VI Folder 53
Stanton, [?] Capt., U. S. N. Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 57
Stanton, Edwin M. Sect. of War Roll I Folder 1
Stanton, Fort (New York) Roll I Folder 1
Stanton, Thaddeus H. Paymaster General Roll IV Folder 35
Starr, Charles G. Capt. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 23, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 36, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 43, Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 52
State, Department of Roll I Folder 6
State of Texas (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 33, Folder 34 Roll V Folder 45
Stearns, George L. Maj., A. A. G. Roll I Folder 1
Stedman, Clarence A. Capt. Roll III Folder 29
Stedman, William Brig. Gen. Roll I Folder 1
Steele, Matthew F. Lt. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 36, Folder 37
Sternberg, George M. Surg. Gen. Roll IV Folder 37 Roll V Folder 46 Roll VI Folder 54
Steunenberg, Frank Roll VI Folder 53
Stevens, Gustane W. S. Capt. Roll III Folder 23
Stewart, Charles Capt., A. A. G. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8
Stillwater (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 36, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 52
Stone, Ray Director of Roads Roll II Folder 18
Stoneman, George Maj. Gen. Roll I Folder 1
Straus, Mathew Roll IV Folder 39
Straussman,, Albert Newsman Roll V Folder 41
Strickland, [?] Roll I Folder 2
Stuart's Avenue for Yellow Fever Roll IV Folder 35
Suarez, Vicente Pardo Roll VI Folder 55
Sumner, Edwin V. Brig. Gen. Roll VI Folder 53, Folder 54
Sumner, McKenzie Lt. Roll I Folder 1
Sumner, Samuel S. Brig. Gen. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 26, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 45
Sumter, Fort Roll VI Folder 53
Supreme Court, United States Roll IV Folder 32
Suwanee [?] (U. S. Boat) Roll III Folder 21 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 43, Roll VI Folder 52
Swartz, [?] Roll IV Folder 37
Swedish and Norwegian Consul, Augustine, Mr. Isadore Roll III Folder 25
Swift, Charles J. Roll III Folder 26
Swobe, Thomas Capt. Roll V Folder 46, Folder 48
Tabor, J. A. Roll VI Folder 49
Taggert, Elmore F. Capt. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 33, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 44, Folder 48, Folder 49 Roll IV Folder 52
Tampa Daily Herald (Newspaper) Roll II Folder 16
Tampa Daily Tribune Roll II Folder 16
Tampa, Florida Roll I Folder 9 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 25, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 38, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 57
Tampa, Fort Roll V Folder 48
Tarpon (U. S. Ship) Roll V Folder 44
Taylor, Charles Roll VI Folder 53
Taylor, H. C. Capt., U. S. N. Roll III Folder 20 Roll VI Folder 57
Taylor, Joseph H. Maj., A. A. G. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7
Taylor, W. G. Scripps McRae League Roll II Folder 16
Teagen, [?] Roll I Folder 2
Tenth Cavalry Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19 Roll IV Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 42 Folder 45, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 52
Tenth Infantry Roll II Folder 13, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19 Roll IV Folder 37 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 52
Teresita Roll I Folder 7
Terrett, Fort (Texas) Roll I Folder 2
Territory Surrendered Roll IV Folder 33
Terror (Spanish Torpedo Boat) Roll III Folder 27
Terry, T. W. Roll I Folder 1
Texas Border Committee Roll I Folder 2
Texas, Department of Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 7, Folder 8 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 57
Texas (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 21, Folder 25 Roll VI Folder 52
Theaker, Hugh A. Col. Roll II Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 33, Folder 37
Third Artillery Roll I Folder 10 Roll III Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 40
Third Cavalry Roll II Folder 13, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19 Roll IV Folder 37, Folder 40, Folder 42 Roll V Folder 45, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 52, Folder 54
Third Infantry Roll II Folder 16, Folder 19 Roll III Folder 24 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 44 Roll VI Folder 52
Third Ohio Vol. Infantry Roll II Folder 14, Folder 17
Third Pennsylvania Vol. Infantry Roll II Folder 17
Thirteenth Infantry Roll II Folder 13 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 37 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 45, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 52
Thirty-eigth Article of War Roll IV Folder 35
Thirty-first Michigan Vol. Infantry Roll VI Folder 54
Thirty-fourth Michigan Vol. Infantry Roll III Folder 23, Folder 24 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 37, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 47, Folder 49
Thirty-second Michigan Vol. Infantry Roll II Folder 15, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 19
Thirty-third Michigan Vol. Infantry Roll III Folder 23, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 51
Thomas, Charles S. Gov., Colorado Roll VI Folder 53
Thomas Brooks (Spanish Ship) Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 35, Folder 36
Thomas, George A. G. A. R. Roll V Folder 46
Thomas, George H. Maj. Gen. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8 Roll VI Folder 57
Thompson, John T. Lt. Roll II Folder 11, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17 Roll IV Folder 36
Thompson, Richard E. Capt. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 17
Thompson's Station, Action of, Tennessee Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8 Roll IV Folder 30 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 54, Folder 56, Folder 57
Thorpe, Wesley C. Capt. Roll I Folder 1
Thurston Rifles, Associate Members of Omaha Roll VI Folder 53
Ticonderoga Roll I Folder 8
Tillinghast, C. Whitney Roll V Folder 48
Tillman, Benjamin J. Lt. Roll V Folder 47, Folder 48
The Times (Cuban Newspaper) Folder 77
Times Union (Tampa Newspaper) Roll II Folder 17
Tolman, Corinne Roll III Folder 27
Toral, Jose Gen., Sp. Forces Commander in Chief Roll III Folder 22, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 51, Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 55, Folder 56
Torney, George H. Surg. Gen. Roll IV Folder 26
Tournat (U. S. Lighter) Roll III Folder 22
Town, Francis Col. Roll I Folder 8
Town, John Roll I Folder 7
Townsend, Edward D. Col., A. A. G. Roll I Folder 1
Trans Atlantic Company Roll IV Folder 33, Folder 34
Trans Mississippi and International Exposition Roll V Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 50
Treah, Char;es G. Capt., A. A. G. Roll V Folder 48
Treasury Department Roll VI Folder 54
Treat, Charles G., Lt. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14
Trevino, Mrs. Roll I Folder 8
Triton (Spanish Ship) Roll IV Folder 40
Troops in Campaign Regulations for the Army of the U. S. Roll III Folder 20
Traux, Charles Chairman, Executive Committee, National Peace Jubilee Roll V Folder 48
Tucker, William F. Maj. Roll II Folder 16
Tullidge, Frank G. Lt., A. A. G. Roll I Folder 1
Turner, Henry L. Col. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 18 Roll III Folder 27, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 40
Tweedale, John Roll VI Folder 51
Twelfth Infantry Roll II Folder 13, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 37 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 52
Twentieth Infantry Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 24 Roll IV Folder 37 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46 Roll VI Folder 52
Twentieth Kansas Vol. Infantry Roll VI Folder 53
Twentieth New York Vol. Infantry Roll VI Folder 52
Twenty-fifth Infantry Roll II Folder 11, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 33, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 52
Twenty-first Infantry Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19 Roll IV Folder 37 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 52
Twenty-fourth Infantry Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 23 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 52, Folder 54, Folder 57
Twenty-second Infantry Roll I Folder 1 Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 52
Typhoid Fever Roll IV Folder 36, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 44, Folder 47, Folder 48
Uncle Sam (U. S. Tugboat) Roll VI Folder 57
Underwriter (U. S. Ship) Roll IV Folder 39
Union Battalion (Spanish) Roll III Folder 27
Unionist (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 23, Folder 26 Roll V Folder 44, Folder 45
Upson, Charles Roll I Folder 1
Utley, [?] Col. Roll VI Folder 57
Uvalde Roll I Folder 5, Folder 6
Vail Brothers Solid Comfort for the Feet Roll V Folder 45
Vaillant, John Col. Roll II Folder 24
Valdez, Pedro A. Roll I Folder 5
Vandercook, Robert Roll I Folder 9
Van de Water, John L. Roll I Folder 10
Van Dorn, [?] Roll IV Folder 30 Roll VI Folder 57
Van Duyn, [?] Surg. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 7
Van Horne, William M. Maj. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37 Roll VI Folder 50
Vaquero, [?] Col. Roll III Folder 23
Vara del Rey, Antonio Capt., Sp. Forces Roll III Folder 25
Vara del Rey, Joaquin Gen., Sp. Forces Roll III Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25 Roll VI Folder 52
Vega, [?] Gen., Cuban Forces Roll II Folder 26
Vernon, Edward Vice Admiral, British Navy, 1740 Expedition Roll VI Folder 53, Folder 56
Vesuvius (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16
Victoria de las Tunas, Cuba Roll I Folder 9
Victoria, Queen of England Roll II Folder 14 Roll VI Folder 52
Viele, Charles D. Lt. Col. Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 49
Vigilancia (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 38, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 44 Roll VI Folder 52
Vigo, Spain Roll IV Folder 33
Villaverde (Spanish Ship) Roll V Folder 44
Villegas, Manuel Romero Capt. de Guardia Civil Roll III Folder 25
Vincint Plantation, Cuba Roll II Folder 18
Viscaya (Spanish Cruiser) Roll III Folder 22, Folder 24, Folder 25
Vixen (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 21 Roll V Folder 52
Volunteers Spanish Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 44
Von Goetzen, Count Lt., Military Attache, Germany Roll VI Folder 52
Von Moltke, Helmuth Field Marshall Roll V Folder 45
Von Ribeur Paschurtz, [?] Commander, Lt., Naval Attache Germany Roll VI Folder 52
Von Schrader, Alexander Lt. Col. Roll I Folder 1
Wade, James F. Maj. Gen. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 17 Roll VI Folder 57
Wadsworth, Fort (New York) Roll V Folder 47
Wagner, Arthur L. Lt. Col. Roll I Folder 9 Roll II Folder 16, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 23, Folder 26 Roll VI Folder 54
Wainwright, Robert P. P. Capt. Roll III Folder 21
Walker, William Filibusterer to Nicaragua Roll V Folder 44 Roll VI Folder 53, Folder 56
Waller, Edwin C. Roll III Folder 27
Walton, Clifford S. Maj. Roll VI Folder 53
Ward, Charles R. Roll I Folder 7
Ward, Henry C. Roll V Folder 47
Ward, Milo B. Maj., Surg. Roll I Folder 5
War, Department of Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 21, Folder 22 Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 48, Folder 49 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 51, Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 54, Folder 57
Warren, Fort (Massachusetts) Roll II Folder 13 Roll VI Folder 51
Warren, H. H. Lt. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
City of Washington (U. S. Ship) Roll VI Folder 52
Washington Post (Newspaper) Roll VI Folder 54
Wasp (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 21 Roll VI Folder 52
Watlus, Gordon W. President of the Omaha Exposition Committee Roll V Folder 50
Watson, J. C. Commodore, U. S. N. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11 Roll III Folder 20 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 43
Webb, G. Creighton Maj. Roll III Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 34, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 49 Roll VI Folder 54
Weiler, J. J. Roll III Folder 26
Weinbach, Thomas Capt. Roll I Folder 1
Weissert, [?] Roll VI Folder 55
Wessels, Henry W., Jr. Maj. Roll II Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
West, Parker W. Capt. Roll II Folder 13 Roll III Folder 22, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 36, Folder 37
Wester, [?] Capt., Military Attache Sweden and Norway Roll VI Folder 52
Western Union Company Roll I Folder 10, Folder 12, Folder 13
Weston, John F. Col. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 21, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 53, Folder 54
West Point, Battle of Roll I Folder 1 Roll VI Folder 57
Wheaton, Lojd Gen. Roll II Folder 12 Roll VI Folder 54
Wheeler, Daniel D. Maj. Roll II Folder 12
Wheeler, Joseph Maj. Gen. Roll II Folder 11, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 54, Folder 57
Wheeler, Joseph, Jr. Lt. Roll III Folder 24 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 46
Wherry, William M. Lt. Col. Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31 Roll V Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 50
Whitcomb, Elisha Capt. Roll I Folder 8
White, Mrs. J. Harrison Roll V Folder 45
Whiteside, [?] Maj. Roll I Folder 8
Whitney, Casper Roll VI Folder 52
Whitney (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 11, Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 31 Roll VI Folder 52
Wikoff, Charles A. Col. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 16 Roll V Folder 44
Wikoff, Camp (Long Island) Roll II Folder 11 Roll V Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50
Wilcox, Marrion Roll V Folder 45
Wilkins, Harry E. Maj. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Williams, A. P. Roll I Folder 8
Williams, Charles A. Capt. Roll IV Folder 37
Willson, David B. Maj. Roll III Folder 19, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 35, Folder 40
Williston, Edward B. Brig. Gen. Roll V Folder 45
Wilmington (U. S. Ship) Roll I Folder 10
Wilson, C. Irving Maj. Roll I Folder 5
Wilson, George W. Roll II Folder 17
Wilson, James W. Sect., Department of Agriculture Roll VI Folder 54
Wilson, Reverend John Roll VI Folder 53
Winslow, Eben E. Lt. Roll II Folder 13
Winter, Francis A. Roll IV Folder 37
Wirth, [?] General Correspondence Roll III Folder 26, Folder 30